- Why?
- Come on.
You were gonna go in a rocket
designed in the 1960s by the Russians.
(Howard:)Yeah, so?
(Leonard:)When was the last time
you heard someone say:
"Ooh, check out this Blu-ray player.
It must be good, it was buiIt in Russia"?
(Howard:)Well, their technology isn't that bad.
(Raj:)When you come back to Earth in a Soyuz
capsule, you free-fall from space...
(Raj:)...at 500 miles per hour, and the only
thing that slows you down...
...is a parachute that pops out
before you crash into the ground.
The thing was designed
by the same brilliant minds...
(Raj:)...who were unable to capture
Rocky and Bullwinkle.
(Howard:)All right, well, whatever.
l wasn't worried.
(Raj:)You weren't?
Okay, let me explain
the difference between you and me.
(Howard:)You watch Star Trek, I live it.
Oh, I don't remember
the episode of Star Trek...
(Raj:)...where the guy never goes to space
and brags about it in a tuxedo store.
(Howard:)Make all the jokes you want, but there's
only one of us brave enough...